yeswevibe.com 2019-05-23

# Privacy Policy - YesWeVibe

YES WE VIBE PRIVACY POLICY

Definitions

”Non-Personal Information” (NPI) is information that is in no way personally identifiable and that is obtained automatically when you access our Website with a web browser.“

Personally Identifiable

Information” (PII) is non-public information that is personally identifiable to you and obtained for us to provide you with a product or service. PII may include information such as your name, address,phone number, credit card information, and other related information that you provide to us.

Our Commitment to Your Privacy

Our Privacy Policy tells you what PII we may collect from you, how we may share your PII, and how you can limit our sharing of your PII.Yes We Vibe is committed to the security and privacy of all our customers. We take your privacy seriously, and we will work with you to ensure that you have an enjoyable online experience. Yes We Vibe and our affiliates respect your privacy and recognize the need for appropriate protection and management of your PII you share with us.

Links to Other Websites

Our Website may contain links to other websites. You understand that these websites are not under our control and are not subject to our Privacy Policy. These websites will likely have their own privacy policies. We have no responsibility for these websites and provide links to these websites solely for your convenience. You acknowledge that your use and access of these websites is solely at your own risk. It is your responsibility to check the privacy policies of these websites to see how they treat your personal information.

Information We Collect

Generally, you control the amount and type of information you provide to us when using our Website. As a visitor to our Website, you can browse our Website to find out more about us. You are not required to provide us with any PII as a Visitor. However, if you register as a Member to use our Website, you must provide PII in order for us to provide you with various features and/or functionality from our Website. As a Member, we collect your PII in the following ways:

At Member Registration

When you register for membership, we collect your name and email address {and other information listed}.

Online Forms

There may be online forms used in our Website. The information you enter into these online forms may contain PII.

Premium Features

Our Website may offer premium features for which you must pay to use. If we were to charge you for the use of these premium features, we would need to collect payment source information (i.e. credit card) to bill you for using such premium features.

Computer Information Collected

When you use our Website, we automatically collect certain computer information by the interaction of your mobile phone or web browser with our Website. Such information is typically considered NPI. We may also collect any of the following:

Cookies  

Our Website uses Google Analytics and “Cookies” to identify the areas of our Website that you have visited. Aside from the approximate location (IP address), the information collected by Google Analytics is mostly anonymous traffic data including browser information, device information, language. A Cookie is a small piece of data stored on your computer or mobile device by your web browser. We use Cookies to personalize the Content that you see on our Website. Most web browsers can be set to disable the use of Cookies. However, if you disable Cookies, you may not be able to access functionality on our Website correctly or at all. We never place PII in Cookies.

Web Beacons

We may also use a technology called, web beacons, to collect general information about your use of our Website and your use of special promotions or newsletters. The information we collect by Web Beacons allows us to statistically monitor the number of people that open our emails. Our Web Beacons are not used to track your activity outside of our Website. We do not link NPI from Web Beacons to PII without your permission.

Automatic Information

We automatically receive information from your web browser or mobile device. This information includes the name of the website from which you entered our Website, if any, as well as the name of the website to which you’re headed when you leave our website. This information also includes the IP address of your computer/proxy server that you use to access the Internet, your Internet Website provider name, web browser type, type of mobile device, and computer operating system. We use all of this information to analyze trends among our Users to help improve our Website.

How Information is Used

We use PII that you provide for our internal purposes, such as offering our services to you, confirming and tracking your order, subscription or registration; analyzing statistics and demographics; and informing you of new products, services, and offers as provided by us and/or our affiliates. Our affiliates may have products, services, or offers about which you may be interested in receiving information and they may use the PII we have for you to contact you. If you don’t want to receive information from our affiliates, you can let us know so you’re no longer contacted by our affiliates about their products, services, or offers.

We may also combine information you give us online or through printed forms; publicly available information; and information we receive from other parties. We use this combined information for your online experience and to let you know about new products, services, offers, and other promotion. To give you the best possible service, we may use our affiliates to provide contracted services for our business, including, but not limited to processing credit cards, hosting our website, shipping products to you, or advertising. In many cases, we will need to provide some if not all the PII you provide to use so our affiliates can perform these services. Our affiliates are only authorized to use your PII as provided within this Privacy Policy.

There are times that we may have to disclose your PII to comply with state and federal laws; to assist  law enforcement and governmental agencies in preventing or investigating fraud or other crimes, or in response to a court order. In such instances, we will only provide the PII requested and your PII will only be used for legal purposes as opposed to marketing.

Finally, if we sold or transferred our business, we would transfer your PII to the purchaser as appropriate and might also retain a copy of your PII for any new business ventures we would start.

Changing Your Information

You may change your PII at any time using facilities found on our Website. If you need assistancewith updating your PII or removing yourself from our mailing lists, just send us an email with your request or contact us using the Contact us information found on our Website.

Opting Out Of Sharing Information  

You can always opt out of future unaffiliated third-party disclosures of your information. Such opt-out will not affect disclosures otherwise permitted by law including but not limited to: (i) disclosures to affiliates, (ii) disclosures to third-party service providers who provide certain services for our business, such as credit card processing, computer system services, shipping, data management, or promotional services, (iii) disclosures to third parties as necessary to fulfill your requests, (iv) disclosures to governmental agencies or law enforcement departments or otherwise required to be made under applicable law, (v) previously completed disclosures to third parties, or (vi) disclosures to third parties in connection with subsequent contests or promotions you may choose to enter, or third-party offers you may choose to accept.

Protecting Your Child’s Privacy

We follow the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). Even though our Website is not designed for use by anyone under the age of 18 (child), we realize that a child may attempt to access our Website. We do not knowingly collect PII from a child. If you are a parent or guardian and believe your child is using our Website, please contact us. We may ask for proof of identification before we remove any information to prevent malicious removal of account information. If we discover on our own that a child is accessing our Website, we will delete the information as soon as we discover it, we will not use the information for any purpose, and we will not disclose the information to third parties. You acknowledge that we do not verify the age of our users nor do we have any liability to do so. If you are a child, please seek the permission of a parent or guardian before accessing our Website.

Our Email Policy

We comply with the federal CAN-SPAM Act. You can always opt out of receipt of further email correspondence from us or our affiliates. We will not sell, rent, or trade your email address to any unaffiliated third-party without your permission except in the sale or transfer of our business.

Our Security Policy

We have taken steps to build our Website using sophisticated encryption and authentication tools to protect the security of your PII. When we collect your PII through our Website, we will encrypt your PII before it travels over the Internet using industry standards as established for conducting secure online transactions. We also use industry standard technologies such as secure routers and firewalls to make sure that your PII is safe. Unfortunately, we cannot fully guarantee secure data transmission over the Internet because of its nature. Once we receive your PII, we have industry standard security measures in place to protect against the loss or misuse of your PII, though again, we cannot fully guarantee against such loss or misuse. We strongly urge you to protect any password you may have for our Website and not share it with anyone. You should always log out of our Website when you are done using it, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place.

Use of Credit Cards

You may have to provide a credit card to buy products and services from our Website. We use third-party billing services and HAVE NO CONTROL over these services. We use our commercially reasonable efforts to make sure that your credit card number is kept STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL by using only third-party billing services that use industry-standard encryption technology to protect your credit card number from unauthorized use. However, you understand and agree that we are in no way responsible for any misuse of your credit card number.

Changes to Our Privacy Policy

As necessary to address changes in laws or our business practices, we may modify our Privacy Policy, in whole or in part, to address these changes. We will typically notify users by some message on our Website home page that our Privacy Policy has changed. We will also change the “Last Updated” date at the beginning of this Privacy Policy. Any changes we make to our Privacy Policy are effective as of this Last Updated date and replace any prior Privacy Policies. We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy periodically to make sure you still agree with it.
